Pei Song.
You are still awake.
Not yet.
Then chat with me for a while.
Sure.
What do you want to talk about?
Anything.
What do you want to eat for lunch tomorrow?
How about I cook for you?
But I only know how to make...
Change the subject.
Why don't you tell me
why you initially
started developing this
big data intelligent analysis system?
I initially developed this system
just to improve communication efficiency
and solve interpersonal troubles.
But later I found that
data is cold.
People meeting each other
is destined.
And the process of getting to know each other
is more important than the result.
Will the system you are developing
have any risk of privacy leaks?
Information security,
how should I put it,
is an issue every big data developer
must consider.
It's not about technology,
but professional ethics.
Computers are actually very simple.
What's complex is the human heart.
It depends on who gives the command.
Whether it's AI
or big data applications,
they are just tools.
These tools
must benefit humanity
and promote social development.
But with the development of technology...
Song Shiya, what are you thinking?
Not bad.
Slow down, Grandpa.
Grandpa.
Ningning.
Come, come.
Come meet your sister-in-law.
Song Shiya.
What?
You know each other?
Grandpa,
she is my
classmate.
You kid,
why have I never heard you
mention it before?
I didn't expect such a coincidence.
It seems my big data system
is quite accurate.
Let's sit down first
and chat while eating.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
Okay.
You sit down too.
It's not easy for you
to gather together.
Come, Grandpa.
You sit down too.
Sit, Xiaoning.
Grandpa,
I missed you so much.
I missed you too.
Grandpa,
who is she?
She is...
Song Shiya,
my wife.
Wife?
Brother,
are you kidding me?
How do you have time
to date and get married?
You kid,
we got our marriage certificate three days ago.
Really?
Say it again,
what's her name?
Song Shiya.
How did you and Brother Pei Song meet?
Introduced by our elders.
Grandpa,
when I was little,
didn't you say
I was your granddaughter-in-law?
Grandpa!
All right.
Jingyan,
later,
Grandpa will find you
a better partner.
A thousand times
better than Pei Song.
Ten thousand times.
No.
I want Pei Song.
I want him.
Fang Jingyan.
Please don't mind her.
Our families are old friends.
I've watched her grow up.
That's how she is.
It's fine.
Stop talking, you two.
Song Shiya,
you must convince me today.
Otherwise, you and Pei Song's
marriage,
I won't agree to it.
Okay.
How do you want to play?
These two bottles of liquor,
one for each of us.
Whoever passes out first
loses.
Okay.
It's a deal.
Song Shiya,
Song Shiya.
Shiya,
Shiya.
Song Shiya.
Song Shiya!
Shiya!
Song Shiya,
don't chicken out.
Let me tell you.
Don't pretend to be weak.
If you can't drink anymore,
Shiya,
Pei Song is mine.
Song Shiya.
Song Shiya!
Alright, alright.
I'll drink for her.
You drink.
I'll drink for her, okay?
Pei Song,
I thought you never drank.
It seems
your love for Song Shiya
is true love.